Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Faculty Publications, 1844-1994 RG.1.1
New York University Archives
- Faculty Publications, 21411
  - Stansbury, Howard, Exploration and Survey of the Valley of the Great Salt Lake of Utah, 1852; 247190 (Box 25, Item 20)
  - Muntz, Earl Edward, Race Contact, 1927; 247191 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - Stoddard, Franci Hovey, The Evolution of the English Novel, 1900; 247192 (Box 26, Item 2)
  - Still, Bayrd, Publications, 1935-1942; 247193 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Second Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: 1877, Report of Progress in the Fayette & Westmoreland District of the Bituminous Coal-Fields of Western Pennsylvania, 1878; 247194 (Box 26, Item 4)
  - Stevenson, John. J., Formation of Coal Beds, 1911-1913; 247195 (Box 26, Item 5)
  - Stumpf, Stephen A., Choosing a Career in Business, 1984; 247196 (Box 26, Item 6)
  - Stoddard, Francis H., The Historical Study of English Grammar, 1886; 247197 (Box 26, Item 7)
  - Stoddard, Francis H., References for Students of Miracle Plays and Mysteries, 1887; 247198 (Box 26, Item 8)
  - Nason, Arthur H., Heralds and Heraldry in Jonson's Plays, 1907; 247199 (Box 26, Item 9)
  - Still, Bayrd, Milwaukee: The History of a City, 1948; 247200 (Box 26, Item 10)
  - Vail, Alfred, Early History of the Electro-Magnetic Telegraph, 1914; 247201 (Box 26, Item 11)
  - Archer, Gleason L., History of Radio to 1926, 1938; 247202 (Box 26, Item 12)
  - Still, Bayrd, German Counties in Pennsylvania, 1928; 247203 (Box 26, Item 13)
  - Still, Bayrd, State Constitutional Development in the United States 1829-1851, 1933; 247204 (Box 26, Item 14)
  - Stoianovich, Traian, Land Tenure and Related Sectors of the Balkan Economy, 1600-1800, 1953; 247205 (Box 26, Item 15)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Second Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: 1876, Report of Progress in the Fayette & Westmoreland District of the Bituminous Coal-Fields of Western Pennsylvania, 1877; 247206 (Box 26, Item 16)
  - Still, Bayrd, Milwaukee: The History of a City (copy 2), 1948; 247207 (Box 26, Item 17)
  - Still, Bayrd, Milwaukee: The History of a City, (Second Printing with new preface by the author), 1965; 247208 (Box 26, Item 18)
  - Morse, Samuel F.B., Amir Khan and Other Poems: The Remains of Lucretia Maria Davidson, 1829; 247209 (Box 26, Item 19)
  - Nason, Arthur Huntington, Talks on Theme Writing and Kindred Topics, 1909; 247210 (Box 26, Item 20)
  - Wehle, Harry B., Samuel F.B. Morse American Painter, 1932; 247211 (Box 26, Item 21)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Varia (Various Publications), 1877-1920; 247212 (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Geological Memoirs (Various Publications), 1871-1893; 247213 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Smith, Homer W., Man and his Gods, 1952; 247214 (Box 27, Item 3)
  - Stevenson, John J., Geology of Northeastern New Mexico, 1881; 247215 (Box 27, Item 4)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Second Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: 1875, Report of Progress in the Greene and Washington District of the Bituminous Coal-Fields of Western Pennsylvania, 1876; 247216 (Box 27, Item 5)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Second Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: Report of Progress T2, The Geology of Bedford and Fulton Counties, 1882; 247217 (Box 27, Item 6)
  - Still, Bayrd, Mirror for Gotham, 1956; 247218 (Box 27, Item 7)
  - Stevenson, John J., The Carboniferous of the Appalachian Basin, 1903-1907; 247219 (Box 27, Item 8)
  - Stunkard, Horace W., Publications, 1934-1940; 247220 (Box 27, Item 10)
  - Stevenson, John J., Interrelations of the Fossil Fuels, 1916-1921; 247221 (Box 27, Item 9)
  - Stunkard, Horace W., Publications, 1915-1932; 247222 (Box 27, Item 11)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Report on Geology of Colorado in 1873, 1874; 247223 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Sihler, E.G., Annals of Caesar: A Critical Biography with a Survey of the Sources, 1911; 247224 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - Sinding, Paul C., History of Scandinavia, 1866; 247225 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Nason, Arthur Huntington, James Shirley Dramatist, 1915; 247226 (Box 28, Item 4)
  - Sihler, E.G., Cicero of Arpinum, 1914; 247227 (Box 28, Item 5)
  - Zurcher, Arnold J., Constitutions and Constitutional Trends since World War II, 1951; 247228 (Box 28, Item 6)
  - Reid, James D., The Telegraph in America, 1879; 247229 (Box 28, Item 7)
  - Stevenson, J.J., Varia 2 (Various Publications), 1872-1909; 247230 (Box 28, Item 8)
  - Meredith, Albert B., Madden, John T., MacCracken, John H., Bouton, Archibald L., Obligations of Universities (Various "Addresses and Discussion"), 1933; 247231 (Box 28, Item 9)
  - Morse, Edward Lind, Samuel F.B. Morse, Letters and Journals, 1914; 247232 (Box 28, Item 10)
  - Millican, Charles Bowie, Spenser and the Table Round, 1932; 247233 (Box 28, Item 11)
  - Stahl, William Harris, Macrobius, Commentary on the Dream of Scipio, 1952; 247234 (Box 28, Item 12)